你还是和我共事  而我是芝加哥的恶人之一
You work right next to one of the worst men in Chicago.
要我们送去入库吗
You want us to voucher for you?
不用  我来办就行
No, I'll take care of it.
我不是告密者
I'm not a rat, man.
你姐姐开车醉驾被抓
The second your sister got popped for that DUI,
我们想偷偷处理掉
we tried to make it all go away.
你可能因为这个进监狱的
You could go to jail over this.
你想要什么
What do you want?
你的眼睛  你的耳朵
Your eyes, your ears.
我得去见一个线人
I gotta go meet a CI.
可能需要支援
I could use a backup.
我们要见的是谁
Who are we meeting now?
看我没用  孩子
No use looking at me, kid.
去吧
Go.
你只能二选一
You're gonna go one way or the other.
-警长  我...  -停
- Sarge, I, uh-- - Stop.
别来这套
You don't get to play this one.
我发誓  我别无...
I swear to you, I didn't have a--
别无什么
Have a what?
选择吗
A choice? Hmm?
那是我的家人
It was my family.
我亲姐姐  他们要带走她的儿子
My kid sister. They were gonna take her son.
我知道他有什么把柄
I know what he's got on you.
那我没办法
There's nothing I can do about that.
-你给了伍兹什么  -没有
- What did you give Woods? - Nothing.
我发誓
I swear to you.
我给了他霍斯特德打架的视频
I tried to give him a BS video of Halstead in a fight.
但他没上钩  他想要更多
He didn't bite. He wanted more.
所以犯罪现场的那两万块钱是他干的
So the money at the crime scene--the 20K--that was him.
是我
It was me.
但我没把视频给他
But I didn't give him the tape.
就我看来你有两条路
The way I see it, you got two choices.
把我卖给伍兹
Serve me up to Woods,
或者你帮我干掉他
or you can help me take him out.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
警长  我站在你这边
Sarge, I am with you.
一直都是
I've always been with you.
翻译     西之   风城章鱼X   Lynn_宁
翻译     H小欠   小萝莉   圈圈
校对     圈圈
可以了吗  没事了吧
Is that it? Are we good?
我可没说没事了
I didn't say that.
时间轴     chance-coco   西查
后期     8T
总监     圈圈
不可能
That is not true.
她不是那样的人  那家伙很喜欢她
Okay, that's not who she is. That guy just really liked her.
他给了她五百
He gave her $500, like,
就在上床后十分钟吧
ten minutes after having sex with her.
这叫做招妓
That's called "Prostitution."
他让她去买条裙子
He told her to go get a dress.
他们那晚出去了  那是大方
They were going out that night. It's called being generous.
瑞安  拜托  说句话好吗
Ryan, please, would you say something?
我可不会碰
I'm not going anywhere near that one.
那就是说他站我这边
That means he agrees with me.
不  那是说他中了你的魔咒
No, that means he's under your spell.
-我得走了  -拜托  别啊
- I should get going. - Come on, stay.
凌晨两点半了
It's like 2:30 in the morning.
我还要早起
I gotta be up early.
我给你看个东西
Let me show you something.
等等  是可卡因吗
Is that-- Wait, is that coke?
抱歉  黏在我口香糖上了
I'm sorry, it's on my gums.
-我真的得走了  -好吧
- I really gotta go. - Mm, fine.
你在这里的时候感觉好多了
It's just, things are always better when you're here,
和我在一起
with me.
真有意思
That was so funny.
-抱歉  -没关系
- Oh, sorry. - No worries.
卡米拉  你跑哪去了
Yo, Camila, where you been hiding?
-我真的要走了  -我和你一起去
- I'm really going this time. - I'm coming with you.
我去和大家说一声
Let me just say bye to everyone.
好吧  我在外面等你
All right, I'll meet you outside.
好
Okay.
我找了你一小时了
I've been looking for you for, like, an hour.
卡米拉·维嘉
卡米拉  是我  我在外面  我们走吧
Camila, it's me, I'm outside. Let's go.
老兄  你没事吧
Hey, man, you all right?
-我没撞到她  我发誓  -什么
- I didn't hit her, I sweared. - What?
她在地上爬
She was crawling across the street.
报警  快报警
Call 911. Call 911!
枪伤  什么
Gunshots... What?
见鬼
Damn it.
没事了...
It's okay, it's okay. It's okay.
你会没事的  谁干的
You're all right. Who did this?
坚持住  坚持住
All right, just hang in there. Hang in there.
救援快到了
Help's on the way.
你会没事的
You're okay. You're okay.
你不是一个人...
You're not alone. You're not alone.
瑞安  瑞安  怎么回事
Ryan. Ryan! What happened?
我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
你快走  你不能在这里
You gotta go. You can't be here.
-我该怎么做  -不  你嗑药了
- What can I do? - No, you're high.
警察马上就会到这里
And the cops are about to be all over this place.
你快点离开这里  快走
Just get out of here. Go!
博伊特  是我  我需要支援
Voight, it's me... I need help.
芝加哥
警署
第五季
第十集
怎么回事
Hey. What's going on?
女性受害者  两处枪伤
Female victim. Two GSWs.
不  杰  到底怎么回事
No, Jay. What's going on, meaning,
你怎么会在这里
what the hell are you doing here?
好吧  我当时在这里接触线人
All right, so I was here, working a CI.
什么线人
What CI?
卡米拉·维嘉  面纱俱乐部的
Camila Vega, from the Veil Club.
绑架案的姑娘吗
The girl from the kidnapping case?
路易斯的妹妹
Luis' sister?
没听过
News to me.
她备案了吗
She on paper?
没有
No.
受害人在派对上吗
Was the victim at the party?
-我觉得是  -你觉得是
- Yeah, I believe so. - You believe so.
你喝酒了  还有吗
You've been drinking. Anything else?
只是喝酒了
Just drinking.
好  回局里去  别对任何人说话
Okay, go back to the office. Don't talk to anyone.
写好你的调查报告
Write up your IPR.
你去看看尸体  我去和凶案组聊聊
Okay, work the body. I'll talk to homicide.
明白
Copy.
什么情况
What do we got?
两处枪伤  第一枪中了胸口
Two GSWs. First shot, center mass.
第二枪在肋骨
Second, lodged in her spine.
发现钱包或者身份了吗
Find a purse, ID?
没有  好吧
Nothing. Okay.
如果这是抢劫  那做得太不干净了
Well, if this was a robbery, they didn't do a very good job.
调查报告写了吗
You write up that IPR?
好
Okay.
我在不经意接近她
I was working her as an unwitting.
她在面纱工作
She works at Veil.
那里有很多毒品交易
A lot of drugs move through that place.
她和我说过派对  我看到了机会
She told me about the party. I saw an opportunity.
但你说得对
But you're absolutely right.
我该先登记她的
I should've put her on paper first.
我搞砸了
Uh, I screwed up.
你在和这个女的上床吗
Are you sleeping with this girl?
没有
No.
好吧
Okay.
记档  开始查案吧
Document it. Start working the case.
你已经跟这个女的混熟了
You're already working the girl.
倒不如继续卧底
May as well stay under.
查清楚是谁杀了那个女的  好吧
Figure out who killed this young woman, right?
好
All right.
我正要联系你呢
Hey, I was just trying to call you.
喝完了  再来一杯吗
You good? You need another?
不了  我要走了
No, I'm leaving.
好  这位是瑞安
Cool. Uh, this is Ryan.
瑞安  这是华莱士
Ryan, this is Wallace.
-那今晚见  -没准  到时再联系
- See you later on tonight? - Maybe. I'll be in touch.
他以前在这上班
He used to work here.
到底怎么了
So, what the hell happened?
警察带我到局子里讯问
The cops took me down to the station.
他们开始拿问题问我  比如
They started drilling me with questions, like,
我有没有看见什么
did I see anything?
我知不知道被杀的女孩是谁
Did I know the girl that got killed?
那女的真死了
Really, she's dead?
你知道她的名字吗
Did you know her name?
麦基
Maggie.
姓什么不清楚
Don't know her last name.
她也参加派对了吧
She was at the party, right?
你看见她和谁走了吗
Did you see who she left with?
是这样  他们问我知不知道
Look, they were asking me if I saw...
-瑞安  我没有  -什么可疑的事
- Ryan, I didn't... - Anything suspicious.
我没看见她走  好吗
I didn't watch her leave, okay? I--
好吧  抱歉
All right, I'm sorry.
真不敢相信她死了
I can't believe she's dead.
我从没见过别人被打死
I've never seen anybody get shot before.
你还好吗
You okay?
只要你在  就好
It's always better when you're here.
真的  什么痕迹都没有吗
Really? No traces of anything?
没有  毒检完全正常
No, tox was clean.
她体内没有毒品或酒精
No drugs or alcohol in her system.
所以死在西洪堡派对上的瘾君子
So our junkie that died at a West Humboldt party
死之前居然是清醒的
died completely sober.
那性侵犯呢  有什么痕迹吗
What about sexual assault? No signs of that?
没有 没撕裂伤  也没有体液
No, no tearing. No body fluids.
没有任何其他人的基因痕迹
No trace of anyone else's DNA.
不过紫外灯确实发现了什么
But UV light did pick up this.
回音
"Echo."
我问了回音俱乐部的保镖
I talked to the bouncer from Club Echo.
他说麦基最近经常进出
He says Maggie comes in all the time.
他记得是因为他老是吼她
He remembers because he's always yelling at her.
这女孩小小的身板
Girl's a hundred pounds.
却直接进这种俱乐部
Walks to the dank-ass club
周围全是高头大马的壮汉
through the filthy-ass hood solo.
这是他原话
These are his words.
我没找到她出门的镜头  但她到达的找到了
I couldn't get her leaving, but I did get her arriving.
说来有点怪
It's a little weird.
这是她准备进入俱乐部
This is her walking up to the club.
然后这里追踪到后门
Tracked her backwards from there,
一直到她从出租车里出来
to where she got out of the cab.
出租车司机说她上了红线威尔逊站
Now the cabby says she got on the Wilson red line.
离回声一个街区就有个下客站
There's an 'L' stop a block away from Echo.
为什么提前下车还上了出租
Why get off early and take a cab?
那个站的摄像头拍到她是在杰克逊站上的车
Yeah, the 'L' camera shows she got on at the Jackson stop.
她还得走一里地去杰克逊站上车
She had to walk a mile to get to Jackson.
就好像她不希望有人
It's like she didn't want someone knowing
知道她要去哪
where she was going.
所以我用了交通探头
So I used the, uh, traffic PODS,
从杰克逊站一路倒查
followed her backwards from the Jackson stop.
看来她当晚是从这里出发的
Looks like her night started right here.
这是西街的一栋公寓
This is an apartment building on Wells Street.
谢谢你  先生  后面的交给我们吧
Thank you, sir. We'll take it from here.
这像是吸毒者的住处吗
Does this look like the apartment of a junkie?
收信人是艾拉·波特
Mail's addressed to Ella Porter.
我没看见有"麦基"或"玛格丽特"
I don't see the name "Maggie" Or "Margaret" anywhere.
-芝加哥警察  -缉毒局  放下武器
- Chicago PD. - DEA, drop your weapon.
好  咱们慢慢来
Okay, let's take it nice and slow.
她说了  我们是芝加哥警察
Like she said, we're Chicago PD.
-我要给你看警徽  -你也给我们看你的
- I'm gonna show you my badge. - While you show us yours.
你们怎么来了
Why are you here?
你们找艾拉有事吗
You got something going with Ella?
-她的化名是"麦基"吗  -是
- Is her cover name "Maggie?" - Yes.
怎么回事  发生什么了
What's going on? Something happened?
艾拉死了
Ella's dead.
今天早上有人开枪打死了她
Someone shot her earlier this morning.
目前还没可靠线索  但好消息是我们有
No, no credible leads yet, but the good news is we've got
一位警探成功打进去卧底了
a detective undercover in this crowd.
他的联系非常可靠  有不少联系人
He's got lots of access. Lots of contacts.
我有信心很快就能找到凶手
I'm confident we'll find the killer very soon.
但我们需要你们的合作
But we'll need your cooperation.
知道动机是什么吗
Any idea what the motive was?
还不知道  我们才着手调查不到半天
No, I mean, we've only been at this 12 hours, but--
我知道你要问什么  吉姆  但我
Look, I know what you're asking, Jim, I--
我懂法律  而且相信我
I understand the law, and believe me,
如果我们查实艾拉的死
if we confirm that Ella was killed
是因为她的卧底工作  会最先通知你们
because of her undercover work, you'll be my first call.
我们会把她的案卷复制给你们一份
We'll get you a copy of her case files,
缉毒局所有案卷
DEA 6s generated,
以及其它我们能想到的资料
and everything else we can think of.
谢谢
Thank you.
不过我有个问题
Question, though.
为什么艾拉昨晚单独行动了
Why was Ella out by herself last night?
不清楚
Not sure.
她没有报备
She was off-book.
麦基的真名叫艾拉·波特
Maggie's real name was Ella Porter.
本地人  两年前加入缉毒局
Grew up in Chicago. Joined the DEA two years ago.
根据我们掌握的信息
Yeah, and based on the information we have,
看起来她是想挖出把毒品分销给
it looks like she was trying to ID the distributor
这五家俱乐部的分销商
supplying cocaine to these five clubs.
她的主要目标是这个人  亚历克斯
Her main target is this guy, Alex.
他是回音俱乐部的经理  也是低端毒贩
He's the manager of Club Echo. Low-level dealer.
他昨晚12点半给艾拉发了一条短信
He sends Ella a text last night at 12:30.
目标
亚历克斯
"我可以给你介绍
"I'll get you the intro you want.
在回音等我  到那咱们再谈"
Meet me at Echo. We'll go from there."
目前我们判断亚历克斯要介绍的就是他的上线
For now, we're assuming that intro was with Alex's source,
也就是那个分销商
the distributor.
所以艾拉大约凌晨1点到了回音俱乐部
So, Ella gets to Club Echo around 1:00 A.M.
目击者证实她和亚历克斯参加了后续派对
Witnesses put her and Alex at the after party at 2:00 A.M.
杰在两点半看到了她
Jay saw her at 2:30.
而她在3点左右进了后巷
And she was in the alleyway around 3:00.
作案窗口并不大
Not a wide window.
我猜是派对上出了什么岔子
Hell, I'm thinking something went wrong at the party
艾拉  亚历克斯和分销商谈崩了
between Ella, Alex, and the distributor.
所以咱们再去一趟回音  找亚历克斯谈谈
So let's go back to Echo, talk to this guy Alex.
把他查个清楚  弄清楚谁是他的供应商
Work his ass. Figure out who his supplier is.
警长  我认识亚历克斯  我通过卡米拉认识他的
Sarge, I know Alex. I met him through Camila.
所以他那里我来搞定吧  私下做个交易
So, uh, let me work him. Make an undercover buy.
好  你和厄普顿一起
Okay. You're taking Upton.
好
All right.
亚当
Adam.
听着  你和伍兹见面的时候...
Listen, when you meet Woods...
-好  -给他他想要的东西
- Right. - Just give him what he wants.
等等  等等  你是让我
Wait, wait-- you want me to give him
把你收钱的录像给他
the tape of you taking the money?
-是的  -老大  我不...
- Yes. - Boss, I don't--
你想让我和你说几次
How many times you want me to tell you?
你说什么就是什么  警长
Whatever you want, Sarge.
还有什么我需要知道的吗
Is there anything else you want me to know?
有
Yeah.
我推荐了阿特沃特
I put in papers for Atwater
所以他是下一个升警探的人  不是你
so he's next in line for detective, not you.
也许你可以利用一下这个
Maybe you can use that.
你想让我们帮你保管吗
You want us to voucher that for you?
不用了  我来搞定
Nah, I'll take care of it.
你确定吗  说实话  我可以搞定的  老大
You sure? Honestly, I can handle it, boss.
那两万块还是没找到  是吗
That 20K is still missing, huh?
是的  我今天早上看了库房记录和ERPS
Yeah, I checked the inventory logs and ERPS this morning.
那是什么让你改变主意的呢
So what prompted this new, enlightened worldview?
愤怒  博伊特摆了我一道
Anger. Voight screwed me over.
告诉我下一个升警探的就是我
Told me I was next in line for detective.
结果今天早上他越过我  升了我的搭档
Found out this morning that he passed me over for my partner.
直接告诉我我是下一个警探
Told me straight up I was next in line.
却越过我升了阿特沃特
And he passes me over for Atwater?
都没有告我一声
Didn't even give me a heads up.
所以在我看来  我什么都不欠他的
So the way I see it, I don't owe him a thing.
天
Man.
亚历克斯  你好啊  哥们
Yo, Alex, what's up, man?
你好啊
Hey, how's it going?
这是我朋友海莉
This is my friend Hailey.
-很高兴认识你  海莉  -我也是
- Nice to meet you, Hailey. - You, too.
你只和漂亮的人一起玩  是吗
You only roll with pretty people, huh?
尽量如此
Try to, anyway.
在我看来  这策略不错
Ask me, it's a solid strategy.
你们俩是想找找乐子吗
You two looking to party?
因为我现在感觉到了特别好的氛围
'Cause I'm feeling some pretty good vibes right now,
尤其是从海莉这里
especially from Hailey.
抱歉  亚历克斯  你不是我的菜
Aw, sorry, Alex. You're not my type.
你可以试试  但她是弯的
You know what? You're welcome to try a little, but she's gay.
我不会评判或者贴标签什么的  瑞安
I don't judge, Ryan. Or label.
咱们喝点吧
Let's get some drinks, yeah?
-好  -好
- Yeah. - Yeah?
-你女朋友呢  -她在面纱工作呢
- So where's your girlfriend? - Oh, she's working Veil.
我可能等等去找她
I might stop by later.
我来这是想看看
Um, yo, I came by 'cause I wanted to see
你能不能给我牵个线
if you could hook me up.
-什么意思  -我想买点货
- What do you mean? - I wanna buy some blow.
-为什么问我  -因为我认识你
- Why are you asking me? - Because I know you.
你和卡米拉更熟
You know Camila better.
她没告诉你
Oh, huh, she didn't tell you?
告诉我什么
Tell me what?
她也卖的
She sells, too.
我只是想
And, I'm just guessing,
她的价格可能更好吧
she'll probably give you a better deal,
毕竟你俩都睡在一起了
since you're sleeping together and all.
哥们  我知道卡米拉做什么
Look, man, I know what Camila does,
但是我不想把生意和乐子混在一起
but I don't like to mix business with pleasure.
-我觉得那会搅得一团乱的  -生意
- I think it makes things messy. - Business?
所以这不只是图个乐子
So this is more than just recreational.
是的  我想干票大的
Yeah, I'm looking to buy some big product.
我有很多想要好货的迫不及待的买家
I got a lot of eager customers who want quality stuff.
实际上  是我们有迫不及待的买家
We have eager customers, actually.
我们是合作伙伴
We're in this together.
你们想要多少
What kind of weight you thinking?
25公斤
Quarter key.
我手头没那么多
I don't have that kind of weight with me.
但我能搞到
I can get it.
九千
Nine grand.
拜托  兄弟  别那么搞我
Come on, man, don't do me like that.
你我都知道价格是八千
We both know eight's the right number.
明天一点来这里见我
Meet me here tomorrow at 1:00.
好  这事只有咱们知道  知道吗
All right. This stays between us, right?
你知道卡米拉也卖货吗
Did you really know that Camila was dealing?
我们现在得谈谈这件事
We're gonna talk about this, now.
我不知道  但我并不惊讶
No, I didn't know, but I'm not surprised.
所以我一直在做她的工作
That's why I've been working her.
你不是在做她的工作  你是在上她
You're not working her, Jay. You're dating her.
现在你把她记录在案了
And you got her on paper now.
你和她在一起是会被开除的
You screwing her is a fire-able offense.
现在她又搅和进来
And now she's mixed up in all this?
什么  接下来你准备和联调局的人撒谎
What, are you gonna lie to the Feds next?
因为我和卡米拉的关系  我们才能走到这一步
My relationship with Camila got us here.
让我们能和亚历克斯做交易
It got us the buy with Alex,
找到指向枪手的线索
who's gonna lead us to the shooter.
所以你的确和她睡在一起了
So, you are sleeping with her?
你要干什么
What are you doing?
我没事  我没事  好吗
I'm fine. I'm fine, all right?
我能查清楚
And I can figure this out.
让亚历克斯带我们去见供应商
Let's let Alex take us to the supplier
可能会带我们找到凶手
who might be good for the murder.
同时  我会和卡米拉谈谈的
In the meantime, I'll talk to Camila,
看看她知道些什么
and I'll see what she knows.
我们得把这事告诉博伊特
We gotta talk to Voight about this.
不  现在还不行
No, not yet.
给我几个小时  拜托
Give me a few hours. Please.
就几个小时
A few hours, that's it.
我们定在明天1点和亚历克斯做交易  也就是说
We set up a buy with Alex at 1:00 p.m. Tomorrow, which means
他得从他的供应商那里买25公斤的货
he needs to buy a quarter key from his supplier.
好  我们已经控制住他了
All right, and we already got him hooked up.
监听了他的手机和一次性电话
We got a wire on his cell and his burner phone.
也定位了他的车
GPS tracker on his car too.
所以只要他一动  我们就能知道
So if this guy moves, we'll know it.
希望能追踪到他的上家
Hopefully we track him to his source.
把他们一网打尽
We can bust them both.
在那之前看好他
Well, we stay on top of him until then.
他一动  我们就动
He moves. We move.
杰去哪了
Hey, where's Jay?
他和卡米拉在一起
He's with Camila.
这就是你要告诉我的全部
That's all you wanna tell me?
他在做他的消息源的工作  警长
He's working his source, Sarge.
想要弄清楚她知道些什么
Trying to figure out what she knows.
要吃点什么吗
Want anything to eat?
我感觉我有十个小时没吃过东西了
I feel like I haven't eaten in, like, ten hours.
你还好吧
You okay?
怎么了
What's wrong?
我和其他人聊过
Look, um, I've been talking to some people,
那个死了的女的  麦基
and that woman who died, Maggie,
她是缉毒局的卧底
she was undercover DEA.
我觉得她可能也在查面纱
I think she was working Veil too.
她是缉毒局的人
She was DEA?
所以如果你知道什么...
So if you know something...
卡米拉  到底是什么情况
Camila, what the hell is going on?
没事  没事  我只是...
Nothing. Nothing, I just--
如果你知道什么  一定要告诉我
Look, if you know something, you gotta tell me, please.
也许我可以帮你
Maybe I can help you.
路易斯死后  我租不起这里
After Luis died, I couldn't afford this place, all right?
我认识一些卖可卡因的人
I knew some people who were selling coke,
所以我就开始买卖
so I started dealing.
就一点点  零零散散的  赚点房租
Just a little, here and there. Just to make rent.
我要进监狱了  是吗
I'm going to jail, aren't I?
不  不会  偶尔卖个八球不会的
No. No, not for selling an eight ball here or there.
当然不会
Absolutely not.
但如果你知道那女人的事
But if you know something about that woman,
那性质就完全不一样了
that is something completely different.
不知道  我当然什么都不知道
No, of course I don't know anything about that.
如果我知道  就会打电话报警了
All right, if I did I would've called the cops.
那你现在为什么这么担心
Then why are you so worried right now?
因为她是联邦的人  瑞安
Because she was a Fed, Ryan.
她那里可能有名单
All right? She was probably taking names.
我得走了
I need to get out of here.
-离开这里  -这样不好
- Leave town. - That's not a good idea.
总比留在这里好  对吗
Look, it's better than staying here, all right?
又没钱又担惊受怕
Broke and scared.
我已经考虑了一段时间了
I've been thinking about it for a while.
路易斯死了  我本来是要走的
After Luis died, I was gonna leave anyway.
可能我就应该走
I probably should have.
但是我  我留下了
But I-- I stayed.
因为你
Because of you.
我爱你
I love you.
真的  虽然像是疯话
I do. Crazy as it is.
他下车了
He's out of the car.
我没看到这里有动静
I don't see any movement down here,
所以也许他是想换一辆车
so maybe he's going down to another car for a handoff.
走进了巷子里  刚过第45街
Walking down the alley, just past 45th.
我就停在街边的巷子头
I'm pulling in the alley down the street.
走向一个车库
Walking up to a garage.
他走向密码锁  是要进车库
He's going for the keypad. He's gonna access the garage.
慢慢来
Keep slow and steady.
我们被发现了  我们被发现了
We've been made. We've been made.
去
Go!
手举起来  手举高
Get those hands up. Get those hands up high.
转过去  转过去
Turn around. Turn around.
-你可以吗  -可以  你去吧
- You got me? - Yeah, you're good.
好了  走吧
All right, let's go.
看上去很安全
We look clear.
该死
Damn it.
好的  找到了
Okay, we might have action.
我找到了半斤可卡因  刚好够数
We got a quarter key, right off the brick.
你找到什么
What you got?
这些是用来开车库门放毒资的
These things open up the drop-off garages for the cash.
里面有六个
There's, like, six of them in here.
这里根本不会有人来
There was never gonna be anyone here.
你别再玩花样了  亚历克斯
You need to stop playing, Alex.
这是谋杀  谋杀联邦特工
This is murder, okay? Murder of a federal agent.
我跟这事没关系
I got nothing to do with that.
"我可以给你介绍
"I'll get you the intro you want.
在回音等我  到那咱们再谈"
Meet me at Echo and we'll go from there."
只是一条短信
It's a text message.
跟死人可没有关系
Had nothing to do with anybody dying.
这条短信足够把你关起来  还有毒品
The text message is enough to lock you up, plus the drugs.
各位  我只是个小人物
Guys, I'm a nobody.
我去车库拿毒品
I go to a garage to pick up blow
和车库的遥控钥匙
and grab a garage door opener.
等我卖掉毒品  就去钥匙上的地址
When I sell the blow, I go to the address on the opener
把毒资放进去
and drop the cash.
没有人  没有名字
No faces. No names.
我没耐心了
I'm losing my patience.
跟我们说说谋杀案那晚的事
Tell us something about the night of the murder,
不然我们就把你关起来
or we're locking your ass up.
我只是介绍人
I was just making an intro.
我每次介绍人过去都能挣一千块
I make a thousand bucks every time I make an intro.
就这样  我就干了这事
That's it. That's all I was doing.
你把她介绍给谁了
Who'd you set her up with?
招我入伙的人
The person who recruited me.
我们需要名字
We need a name.
卡米拉·维嘉
Camila Vega.
很好
Good.
不行  你不能跟她谈
Hey, no. You can't talk to her.
-她现在是嫌犯  -不  她不是
- She's a suspect now. - No, she is not.
她不会做这种事
She would not do something like this.
我了解她  让我跟她谈谈
I know her. Just let me talk to her,
也许我能搞清楚  我能问出个名字
'cause maybe I can figure this out, I can get a name.
杰  不行  你现在不理智
Jay, no, hey. You are not thinking straight.
无论你多么忠于这女孩  都不值得
Whatever loyalty you have to this girl, it is not worth it.
你必须放下
You have to let it go, man.
怎么了
Hey, what's going on?
你有没有打包行李
Hey, do you have a bag packed?
为什么  发生什么事了
Why? What the hell is going on?
拿上你的行李
Grab your bag.
乘城际去格兰特公园旁边的火车站
Take the 'L' to the train station near Grant Park.
别带电话  别开车  我在那里跟你碰头
No phone, no car. And I'll meet you there.
发生什么事了
What happened?
在那里跟我碰头
Just meet me there.
我们得想办法脱身
We have to find a way out of this.
就我和你
Just me and you.
你在这里干什么
Hell are you doing here?
我不知道她跟你说了什么
I don't know what she told you--
你觉得需要她跟我说什么吗
You think she needed to tell me something?
杰  你没那么厉害
Jay, you're not that good.
所以我再问你一次
So I'll ask you again.
你在这里干什么
What the hell are you doing here?
-我要去见卡米拉  -我知道
- I'm going to see Camila. - I know that.
我还不了解你吗
I ran your muds and tolls.
我的问题是  "为什么"
My question is, "Why?"
-去看看她知道什么  -好的
- To see what she knows. - Okay.
我知道的是
Well, here's what I know.
她是缉毒局探员谋杀案的嫌犯
She's a suspect in the murder of a DEA agent.
-她没有杀人  -这你可不知道
- She didn't kill anybody. - You don't know that.
你要让她开口  带上窃听器
You're gonna work her. You're gonna wear this wire.
你要搞清楚她到底知道什么
You're gonna find out exactly what she knows
把她绳之以法
and bury her ass.
你听懂了吗
You understand me?
怎么了  我们为什么要在这里见面
What's going on? Why are we meeting here?
我不明白
I don't understand.
我找过麦克
Look, I talked to Mike.
他说亚历克斯被抓了  我该告诉你
He said Alex got busted and I should tell you.
亚历克斯  你在开玩笑吧
Alex? You gotta be kidding me.
卡米  怎么了
Cam, what is going on?
我撒谎了
I lied, okay?
我不只是一个小人物
I don't--I don't just deal a little, okay?
我招募下线
I recruit dealers.
我把他们跟毒品搭上线
I hook them up with product.
好  那你搞砸了  你在贩毒
Okay, so you messed up. You're moving drugs.
这和缉毒局的探员有什么关系
What does that have to do with the DEA agent?
我当时正通过亚历克斯招募她
I was recruiting her through Alex, okay?
所以当时她才出现在派对现场
That's why she was at the party.
她过来找我的
She came to talk to me.
那你们说上话了吗
Did you? Did you talk?
没有
No.
我当时很紧张
No, I got nervous.
我听到别人叫她另外一个名字
I heard someone call her by a different name.
艾拉
Ella.
所以我告诉我上线这有猫腻
So I told the guy that I work for that something was wrong,
因为她告诉我们的是假名
that she wasn't who she said she was.
然后呢
And then what?
然后她死了
Then she was dead.
你告诉谁了  他的名字
Who'd you tell? What's his name?
-我不能说  -告诉我
- No. - Yeah.
卡米拉  你得告诉我名字
Cam, you gotta tell me his name.
告诉我名字  也许我能帮到你  好吗
You gotta tell me his name. Maybe I can help, all right?
但我得知道是谁向她开了枪
But I need to know who shot her.
你帮不了我  好吗  没人能
You can't help me, okay? No one can.
而且我现在得离开这儿
And I need to get out of here now.
你到底跟不跟我一起走
Are you coming with me? Yes or no?
跟
Yeah.
但我们得先把眼前的事解决了
Yeah, but first we gotta get out in front of this.
我们唯一的办法就是
The only way out of this, for both of us,
拿到你并不知道
is if we get proof you didn't know
他会杀掉她的证据
that dealer was gonna kill her.
他会杀了我  我们俩都会死
He'll kill me. He'll kill both of us.
不  我不会让这种事发生的
No, I am not gonna let that happen.
我爱你
I love you.
我知道我之前没这么说过  但我真的爱你
I know I didn't say it before, but it's true.
他叫华莱士·布莱克
His name is Wallace Blake.
那天你在夜店说话的那个人吗
The guy you were talking to at the club the other day?
现在我们这么办
All right, here's what we're gonna do.
你给他发信息
You're gonna text him,
跟他说要和他在面纱俱乐部见面
and you're gonna tell him to meet you at Veil.
让他这么做吗
Are we gonna let him do this?
让他招认
We're gonna get a confession.
这是唯一为你洗清的机会
It's the only way to clear your name.
这是我们破案的最好机会
It's our best chance at making this case.
我们走
Let's go.
注意  他来了
Eyes up, he's here.
他怎么在这里
Why is he here?
我们要出城  所以他一起来了
We're headed out of town, so he came along.
说吧
All right, so?
有什么事那么重要
What's so important?
我只是想和你说
I just wanna talk to you
那晚的事
about the other night.
不  不在这里说
No, we're not doing that here.
我们得说
Yeah, we are.
你是谁来着
Who the hell are you again?
我们只想做对的事
Yo, man, we're just trying to do what's right.
在我看来  你会比我们失去的更多
The way I see it, you got more to lose than we do,
所以和我们说是为你好
so it's in your best interest to talk to us.
我只想知道如果警察找上我了
I just wanna know what you want me to say
你想让我怎么说
if the cops come get me.
说什么
Say about what?
别装蒜
Don't jerk us off.
我们都知道在说什么
We both know what we're talking about.
你杀的女人  是缉毒局的探员
That woman you shot, she's a DEA agent.
瑞安  你在干嘛
Ryan, what're you doing?
他太急了
Man, he is pushing way too hard.
别急啊  杰
Back off, Jay.
你们肯定是把我和谁弄混了
Well, you must have me confused with someone else.
我可不知道什么死掉的缉毒局探员
I mean, I don't know nothing about a dead DEA agent.
你想像个混混一样走掉吗
You're just gonna walk out of here like a punk?
让开
Get out of my way.
告诉我们
Just talk to us.
闭嘴  让开
Shut up, and get out of my way.
芝加哥警署
Chicago PD.
过来
Come here.
把手背后去
Put those hands back. Get 'em back!
后退点
Back up.
没事吧
You all right?
过来
Come on.
我们走
你有5分钟时间
You got five minutes.
所以你真的是警察
So you're really a cop?
对
Yeah.
我
I'm...
-我不知道怎么说  -你让我恶心透了
- I don't know what to say. - You make me sick.
你知道和一个根本不存在的人在一起
You know what it's like to be with someone
是什么感觉吗
who doesn't really exist?
你知道那感觉吗
Do you know how that feels?
-卡米拉  -走开  别碰我
- Camila. - Get away from me. Don't touch me.
没听到吗  走开
Don't you hear me? Get away from me.
现在
Now.
我没杀那个女的
I didn't kill that lady.
而且当时我不在巷子附近
And I wasn't anywhere near that alley.
你怎么知道她在巷子被害的
How'd you know she was killed in an alley?
-我看报纸  -报纸没报道
- I read the papers. - Wasn't in the papers.
那我就是在别的地方看到的
Well, I read it somewhere.
-我没杀她  -很好
- I didn't kill her. - Good.
卡米拉干的
Camila did.
对  她吓坏了
Yeah, she was freaked out.
她告诉我有人用其它名字叫了那女的
She told me someone called that lady by a different name.
她吓坏了  以为那女人是警察
She seemed scared, thought she was a cop.
我就知道这些
All I know.
你们显然没有足够证据
Y'all obviously don't have enough evidence,
不然不会试图让我供认
else you wouldn't have tried to work a confession out of me.
你们不玩扑克牌的  对吧
You guys don't play poker, do you?
知道吗
See?
关键是
The thing is,
不该让我看到你们的手
you're not supposed to show me your hand.
我听到有人用别的名字叫了麦基
I heard someone call Maggie by a different name.
好吗  好像是艾拉
All right? Ella, I think.
我很慌  因为我猜她是警察
So I panicked because I thought she might be a cop.
我告诉华莱士小心些
I told Wallace to be careful,
但我没想到他会杀了她
but I didn't think he was gonna kill her.
你最后看到艾拉是什么时候
When's the last time you saw Ella?
差不多凌晨3点
Around 3:00 in the morning.
她正和华莱士一起出去
She was heading out the door with Wallace.
这是很有价值的证言
That's good testimony.
问题是  华莱士说杀人的是你
Problem is, Wallace says you killed her.
太扯了  我都没有枪
That's crazy, I don't even own a gun.
这不够
All right, that's not good enough.
你知道吗
You know what?
凶杀案发生时
When the murder was happening,
我在后屋里和你们的同伴亲热
I was in the back room screwing your partner.
够了吗
Is that good enough?
这是你车子的地上的
These are from the floor of your car.
-驾驶人一侧  -没错
- Driver's side. - Yeah.
看到发光的东西了吗
See all that stuff that's glowing?
是血
That's blood.
是艾拉的血
It's Ella's blood.
你的鞋子上肯定也有
Must've been on your shoe.
我不是傻子
I'm not stupid.
你们在虚张声势
You guys are bluffing.
你确定吗
You sure about that?
知道想清除血迹有多难吗
You know how hard it is to get rid of blood?
你可以尽管清洗
I mean, you can wash it,
用吸尘器  再清洗  血...
vacuum it, wash it again, it'll--
律师
Lawyer.
行  但那时我们就帮不了你了
Okay, but then we can't help you.
卡米拉的证词是铁证如山
Camila's words get set in stone.
你杀的可是联邦探员
We're talking about a federal agent here, man.
是死刑
That's the death penalty.
最后的仪式  注射死亡
Last rites, needle in the arm, the whole bit.
所以
So...
现在是你活命的唯一机会
Now, this is your one chance to get out in front of this.
你告诉我们事情经过
Tell your side of the story.
让我们明白你为什么那么做
Just help us understand why you did it.
如果你那样
'Cause you do that,
说出真相
tell the truth,
我们可以找联邦的人谈谈  给你定协议
and we talk to the Feds, make you a good deal.
你...
You know, you--
你想想
I mean you think about it,
这一刻  现在
this moment, right now,
你决定自己的生死
you decide if you live or die.
我知道那个女孩在说谎
I knew that girl was lying.
然后她就走开了
Then she just walked away.
我让她停下
I told her to stop.
她却一直走  我就抓了她
She kept walking, so I grabbed her.
她打了我
She, uh-she hit me.
我就向她开枪了
And I-I shot her.
现在呢  怎么定协议
So? What happens now? How do we make that deal?
不定
We don't.
什么  你说...
What? You said--
我骗你的
I lied.
不过有一件事你的直觉是对的
But you know, your instincts were right about one thing.
照片确实是假的
The photos. They were fake.
看来我们知道怎么玩扑克
So I guess we do know how to play poker.
怎么了
What's going on?
什么...
Wh--hey!
放开
Get off!
你在跟我玩什么把戏
What the hell kind of game are you playing with me?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about!
Gah! I don't know what you're talking about!
博伊特拿的那两万一直都在证据室里
That 20K Voight took was in evidence all along.
什么
What?
管理员说他写错了案件编号
The property clerk said he wrote down the wrong case number,
所以博伊特照章办事了
so Voight played it by the book.
至少这次是
This time, anyway.
但你和我  我们的事还没完
But you and me, we still got some business to do.
明白了吗
Understand?
我问你  明白了吗
I said understand?
明白了
I understand.
警长
You know, Lieutenant,
到底什么事
what is this?
你为什么这么恨博伊特
Why do you hate Voight so much?
恨
Hate?
不是
Nah.
我们是一个笼子里的两条狗  里面只有一碗狗粮
We're two dogs in a cage and one bowl of food.
那不是恨
That's not hate.
而是生存
It's survival.
就这样吗
So that's it, then?
活儿都是我们干的  然后...
We do all the work and the--
联邦的人来把人带走
And the Feds swoop in for the attaboy.
有时候是这样
It's the way it goes sometimes.
对
Yeah.
但你担心的不是那个
But that's not what you're worried about.
你已经尽力了
Look, you did what you could.
杰这次确实过分了
Jay was over his skis on this one.
不怪你
It's not on you.
嗯
Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
你肯定听说了  案子联邦接手了
I'm sure you heard. Feds took the case.
你在找毒品吗  不是吧
Are you seriously looking for drugs right now?
是  毒品  酒精
Yeah. Drugs, alcohol.
或者能解释所发生之事的东西
Or something might explain what the hell just happened.
你别找了  我不吸毒
I'll stop you right there. I don't do drugs.
从没吸过
I never have.
这我保证
You have my word on that.
你的保证没有价值了
Well, your word doesn't mean too much, does it?
我当着你的面问你
Now, I asked you point blank,
跟人家睡了没有
"You sleeping with this girl?"
你看着我的眼睛撒谎了
You looked me in the eye, and you lied.
你让我们整个团队陷入危险
You put this whole unit at risk.
你自己挖了个大坑
And you dug a hell of a hole.
我希望有办法解决
I just hope there's a way out.
他的真名是什么
What's his real name?
不重要了
Doesn't matter.
对我很重要
Does to me.
杰
Jay.
你走运  华莱士招了
You got lucky. Wallace confessed.
你的谋杀嫌疑洗脱了
You're off the hook for the murder.
但你会被起诉毒品分销罪名
But you will be charged with felony drug distribution.
还有可能是谋杀的从犯
And more than likely, accessory to murder.
不过  如果你合作
However, if you cooperate,
我或许可能说服他们网开一面
I can probably convince them to look the other way on that.
帮你免除毒品相关罪名
And help you out with that drug charge.
什么合作
What do you mean "Cooperate?"
不要提关于杰的事
Just keep your mouth shut about Jay.
他就是个进你的酒吧问问题的人
He's a guy that came into your bar, asked questions.
谋杀那晚
The night of the murder,
你跟一群朋友在开派对
you were at a party with a bunch of your friends.
其中一个是瑞安
One of them was Ryan.
然后你发现他是警察
Later, you found out he was a cop.
没有做爱  没有后屋
No sex. No back room.
就好像我从没认识过他吗
What, like I never even knew him?
是的
You didn't.
那样我就给你重新生活的机会
You do that, I'll give you a chance to have a life.
否则我亲手埋葬你
You don't, I'll bury you.
我什么都不会说
I won't say a word.
不是我从没认识过他
Like hell if I didn't know him.
而是你认识的他是个谎言
The person you know, that's the lie.